const tamang = [
    {
      id: "1",
      question: "अगु",
      options: ["काका", "काकी", "मामा"],
      correctAnswer: "काका",
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      question: "कुइ",
      options: ["पानी", "आकाश", "माटो"],
      correctAnswer: "पानी",
    },
    {
      id: "3",
      question: "खुदु",
      options: ["सखर", "मह", "चिनी"],
      correctAnswer: "मह",
    },
    {
      id: "4",
      question: "चेम",
      options: ["सखर", "नाच", "चिनी"],
      correctAnswer: "नाच",
    },
    {
      id: "5",
      question: "छोब",
      options: ["संस्कार", "नाच", "बन्चरो"],
      correctAnswer: "संस्कार",
    },
    {
      id: "6",
      question: "तरी",
      options: ["बन्चरो", "खुकुरी", "तरबार"],
      correctAnswer: "बन्चरो",
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      question: "दली",
      options: ["मान्छे", "घर", "धनुस"],
      correctAnswer: "धनुस",
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      question: "सुफी",
      options: ["ओठ", "चुरा", "नाच"],
      correctAnswer: "ओठ",
    },
    {
      id: "9",
      question: "लाज्या",
      options: ["सानो", "केटो", "हतियार"],
      correctAnswer: "हतियार",
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      question: "बोमो",
      options: ["काठ", "रीस", "समुन्द्र"],
      correctAnswer: "रीस",
    },
  ];
  export default tamang;